John **Chapman**



Contact

- South Park, PA 15236
- \Box (412) 848-8687

Education

Pittsburgh Technical College, Oakdale, PA Associate in Science Degree, Graphic Design, September 2022

Highlights

- Two years of academic experience in the Graphic Design field of study
- Emphasis on working in a production art career with a strong skill set in Adobe InDesign
- Freelance photography and digital editing experience

Software & Industry Training

Software Knowledge

Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe In-Design, Adobe Dreamweaver, Microsoft Office (Word/Excel/PowerPoint), Atom

Areas of Concentration

Digital Illustration, Digital Imaging, Photography, Web Development, HTML, CSS, Corporate Design, Advertising Design, Print Production

Achievements

Recipient- Honor Roll, Pittsburgh Technical College, October 2019-January 2020; January 2020-April 2020 Member, South Park High School Design Club, 2018-2019 Member, South Park High School Baseball Team, 2015-2017

Work Experience

Related Work Experience

Freelance Photographer, Pittsburgh PA, April 2020

Additional Work Experience

Champs Sports, Sales Associate, Pittsburgh PA, November 2019 - September 2021 Olive Garden, Busser, Pleasant Hills, PA, November 2018 - April 2019 Pet Supplies Plus, Store Team Member, Bethel Park, PA, August 2018 - November 2018